{
    "subject": "resource/Lionel_Casson",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/New_York_City",
    "human_readable": "Lionel Casson died in New York City.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8887158036231995,
            "question": "Where did Lionel Casson die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13330860435962677,
            "question": "What is New York City known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1205204650759697,
            "question": "Were there any famous people born in New York City?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10435894131660461,
            "question": "What are some landmarks in New York City?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0981161966919899,
            "question": "What is the history of New York City?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08277948945760727,
            "question": "Why might someone choose to live in New York City?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07967303693294525,
            "question": "Can you name some famous people from New York City?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07691891491413116,
            "question": "What is the population of New York City?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06866790354251862,
            "question": "Is New York City a popular tourist destination?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06359051913022995,
            "question": "What are some cultural attractions in New York City?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lionel Casson died in New York City.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3868_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is New York City a popular tourist destination?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3868_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the population of New York City?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3868_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name some famous people from New York City?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3868_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3868_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3868_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3868_150.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3868_161.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3868_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3868_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3868_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3868_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3868_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3868_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provided confirm that Lionel Casson died on July 18, 2009, and his location of death is listed as Manhattan, NY, which is part of New York City."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe document states that Lionel Casson died July 18 in Manhattan, which is part of New York City. Therefore, the statement \"Lionel Casson died in New York City\" is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}